- 嘿... - 嘿!
- Hey. - Hi.
菲比，出了什么事吗？
Phoebe,what's wrong?
戴着这个超大订婚戒指快要把我累死了！
I'm just so exhausted from dragging around this huge engagement ring.
-噢！天啊！ -恭喜你啊！哇！
- Oh,my God. - Congratulations.
他有没有跪下来？他有准备求婚词吗？
So did he get on one knee? Did he have a speech prepared?
噢！他有哭吗？
Oh,did he cry?
没错，我喜欢求婚，很奇怪吗？
Yeah,big surprise,I like proposals.
实在是很温馨，是我人生中最浪漫的一刻。
Well,it was really sweet,and,like,the most romantic thing ever.
嘿，我们来敬菲比 为了她找到世界上最好的男人干一杯。
Here's to Phoebe,who's found the greatest guy in the world.
敬菲比和...
To Phoebe and..
应该是麦克吧？
I want to say "Mike"?
-敬菲比和麦克！ -喔！
- To Phoebe and Mike. - Hey.
谢谢大家！ 噢对了，我有点东西要给你！
Thank you. Oh,and I have something for you.
这是我的小记事本 里面有我约会过的男生的电话
It's my little black book. It's got the numbers of all the guys I've dated.
噢，菲比。很谢谢你，但我想我用不上了。
Oh,Phoebe,that's nice,but you know what? I think I'm okay.
你还是把它送给你其他独身的女性朋友吧
Give it to one of your other single girlfriends.
我也想，但你是最后一个独身的了
I would,but you're the last one.
那给我吧！
Give me the book!
巴布罗.迪亚斯,
"Pablo Diaz.
布里迪.史密斯
Brady Smith.
“开货车的男生”
Guy in Van"?
那是我的初恋！
Oh,my first love.
巴伯.格里莫的名字旁边标着个X是什么意思？
What is the red X next to Bob Gremore's name mean?
死掉了。
Dead.
没关系，他已经很老了。
Oh,it's okay. No,he was old. Yeah.
他也活够了，他参与了奥马哈海滩（二战诺曼底战役）首轮攻击
And he lived a full life. He was in the first wave at Omaha Beach.
嘿，对不起 我结婚时也应该把我的电话本给你们男生的。
I should've given you guys my black book when I got married.
尽管那不算是电话本，只是一张皱皱的纸...
Although,it wasn't so much a book as a napkin.
...上面写着珍妮丝的电话。
With Janice's phone number on it.
菲比，Jethro Tull不是一个乐队吗？
Phoebe,isn't Jethro Tull a band?
没错。
Oh,yes,they are.
罗斯的科研经费
The.One.With.Ross's.Grant
嘿，亲爱的
Hey,honey.
嘿，甜心
Hey,sweetie.
-莫尼卡不在吗？ -不在。
- Is Monica not here? - No.
那我先告诉你吧，我的经纪争取到一个大广告客户
Then I'll tell you. My agency was bidding for a big account,and they got it.
-这是我第一个跨国广告 -酷！
- It's my first national commercial. - Cool.
不是我吹牛，但很多内容都是我构思出来的！
And I don't want to brag,but a lot of the ideas were mine.
拜托，你有没有在听啊？全部构思都是我的！
Hell,you weren't there. All the ideas were mine.
太好了！嘿，可以介绍我去拍广告吗？
That's great. Hey,can you cast me in it?
...不知道啊，我想你不适合里面的角色。
I really don't think you're right for the part.
怎么会？我可以演任何角色。我是一条变色龙呢！
What do you mean? I can do anything. I'm a chameleon.
我很老！
I'm old.
我很累！
I'm tired.
嘿！我很热！我很冷！ 呵？？拜托，有什么我不能演？
Oh,I am hot. I'm cold. Come on,what can't I do?
我得说，精彩...
First of all,bravo.
但我觉得你真的不适合 这个角色是一个死板的大学教授。
But I don't think you're right for this. The part's a stuffy college professor.
也可以啊！ 你好，我是你们的教授。
I can do that. Hello,I'm your professor.
当我有空或者没有...演讲的时候
When I'm not busy thinking of important things,or professing..
我会用...噢！是什么产品？
I like to use.. What's the product?
电子商务网络解决方案。
Software that facilitates inter-business networking e-solutions.
我很冷！
I'm cold.
- 嘿! - 嘿!
- Hey. - Hey.
猜猜谁有可能得到一笔庞大的科研补助金！
Guess who's a finalist for a huge research grant?
给你个提示，他正在看着你。
I'll give you a hint. He's looking right at you.
除非你说的是那个穿裙子的怪人
Well,unless it's the creepy guy with his hand up his kilt..
恭喜你！
I'm gonna say,"Congratulations."
我实在是太兴奋了，我击败了其他的几百个竞争者
I'm so excited. Apparently,I beat out hundreds of other applicants..
包括我们研究所的五个同事。
including five guys I went to graduate school with.
不是我吹嘘，但...五个人!
Not that I'm keeping score,or anything. Five.
-哇!太厉害了。 - 是啊！
- Wow,that's great. - Yeah.
-那个是什么补助金？ -那是25,000元的补助
- So tell me about the grant. - Well,okay,it's for $25,000.
如果我得到了 那我就可以完成我那领域的研究了。
And if I get it,I'll be able to complete my field research.
然后我就可以在“古生物学刊”里发表我的论文了
And there will be an article about me in the Paleontology Review.
那是我头一次在那本书上发表论文
It'll be the first time my name is in there..
而其他人不会再质疑我的工作了
without people raising serious questions about my work.
-等等，你是说杜瓦基金？ -没错，怎么了？
- Are you talking about the Dewer Grant? - Yeah. Why?
班杰明赫伯管理着那个基金
Benjamin Hobart is administering that grant.
-你的前任男朋友？ -对。
- Your ex-boyfriend? - Yeah.
那么说 你的前男友决定了你现任男友是否能得到那笔钱？
So your ex-boyfriend is gonna determine if your new boyfriend gets this grant?
哇，你的现任男友真草包。
Wow,your new boyfriend is screwed.
没有，我们很愉快的分手的。
No. No,we ended on great terms.
我意思是，如果对你有帮助的话
If anything,I think this could help you. You know what?
我们可以把他约出来吃个饭啊 我可以把你介绍给他。
Why don't we all go out to dinner,and I can introduce you.
-是吗？你觉得有帮助吗？ -当然啦，我给他打电话啦。
- If you think it'd help. - Yeah,absolutely. I'll call him.
那，我可以做什么去...迎合他啊？
Now,is there anything I could do to butter him up?
他喜欢点什么？
Anything he really likes?
唔...他有一整套性变态玩具。
He does have a pretty serious latex fetish.
我知道该怎么做了。
We'll see how dinner goes.
- 嘿! - 嘿，想去看电影吗？
- Hey. - Hey,you want to go see a movie?
我已经告诉过你我今天一整天要打扫 好让麦克搬进来住。
I told you I had to spend all day clearing out stuff so Mike could move in.
- 噢！对哦. - 没错.
- Oh,right. - Yeah.
既然我都来了，我就帮你清洁和收拾一下吧！
Now that I'm here,I might as well help with the cleaning and organizing.
刚好我有打标签机
I just happen to have my label maker.
噢，要丢弃自己的物品太难了！
Oh,it's so hard to get rid of stuff.
你和钱德要同居的时候 有为丢弃东西烦恼过吗？
Did you and Chandler make compromises when you moved in together?
钱德有烦恼过！
Chandler did.
-他想你丢弃什么？ -很多东西啊
- What does he want you to give up? - A bunch of stuff.
我最舍不得的是...他要我丢掉格拉达斯。
And the worst one,he wants me to get rid of Gladys.
谁是格拉达斯？
Who's Gladys?
噢！多么可怕的浪费啊！
What a tragic loss.
就是说。我真的不想放弃她啊。 噢！我想到了，你可以带她走啊！
Yeah,I really hate to give her up. Oh,I know. Oh,you should take her.
这个，我..我也不知道好不好...
I don't know.
-为什么？你不喜欢她吗？ -我当然喜欢她啊。有什么不喜欢的！
- What,you don't like her? - Of course I do. What's not to like?
我可以马上就把她拿走！
I'd take her in a minute.
但我觉得你现在说放弃太早了。
But I think that you're giving up too easy.
我想你应该为她作斗争！
Honey,I think that you need to fight for her.
-你觉得是这样吗？ -当然啦！
- Really,you think? - Absolutely.
你对他说:对不起，麦克。 我不能失去她
You say to him,"I'm sorry,Mike,I can't live without her.
她对我来说很重要
She means too much to me."
好的，我是该为她争取一下。
Okay,I'll fight for her. Okay.
等等，我忽然想到... 如果我这样做，你就无法得到她了。
Oh,wait. I just realized,if I do that,that means you don't get her.
对哦，怎么我没想到呢！
Damn it,I did not think this through.
艾玛,妈妈给你带了小点心
Emma,mom's got a snack for you.
你知道 她有时喜欢些烤肉味的番茄薯片
You know,every now and then,she might like some barbecue potato chips.
-嘿，你们。 -嘿
- Hey,guys. - Hey.
-嘿 -嘿,宝贝
- Hi. - Hey,baby.
推荐有回复了吗？
Oh,any word on casting yet?
-乔伊，我已经说过了，你不适合那个角色。 -什么意思啊？
- I told you,you're not right for the part. - What do you mean?
瑞秋，你会不会花钱 买像我这样的教授介绍的电子货啊？
Rach,don't I seem like a professor you'd buy some kind of e-crap from?
不好意思，我对这种东西没什么兴趣。
I'm sorry,this sounds like something I'm never gonna be interested in.
拜托啦！好像我很为难你似的。
Look,come on,please? It's not like I'm asking you for some crazy favor.
这是我的工作啊，我是个职业的演员呢！
This is what I do for a living. I am a professional actor.
噢！原来我迟到两个小时了！
Man,I'm two hours late for work.
这里有我的一盘带子，里面有我拍过的所有广告。
Here's my reel. It's got all the commercials that I've been in.
-乔... -你就看一下吧
- Joe.. - Just watch it.
如果你不喜欢就别给你上司就是了。
If you don't like it,don't pass it on to your bosses.
-好吧！ -谢谢。
- Fine. - Thank you.
-工作啦，乔！ -可恶！
- Work,Joe. - Damn it.
-我该怎么办啦？ -就给你上司看看咯！
- What am I gonna do now? - Just pass the tape along.
他的确不适合演这个。
He's not right for the part.
如果我推荐他 我的老板会发现我是个傻瓜！
If I suggest him,my bosses will think I'm an idiot.
我希望我的老板能迟些才发现这一点
And that's something they should learn on their own.
那就告诉乔伊你看过带子
Just tell Joey that you watched the tape..
你很喜欢 但你的老板们不喜欢。
and you liked it,but your bosses didn't.
那样，你就成了好人，坏人就是你的老板啦。
Then you're the good guy,and they're the bad guy.
好主意！我喜欢，老板不喜欢。
That's good. I liked it,they didn't.
乔伊，看在上帝份上，去工作啦！
Joey,for God's sake,go to work.
无法相信我能见到班杰明赫伯。
I can't believe I'm about to meet Benjamin Hobart.
我一直以为
I've always thought of him as someone I'd invite..
只有在梦中才能和他共聚晚餐呢
to my fantasy dinner party.
他会不会带上克里斯蒂・布林克利（超级名模）
或者C-3PO（星球大战中的机器人）来呢？
Do you think there's any chance he'll bring Christie Brinkley or C-3PO?
对不起，看来他只孤身一人。
Sorry,it looks like it's just him.
查莉！(格雷戈・金尼尔 演员/节目主持人）
Charlie.（Gregory Kinnear）
天啊，你简直美得让我头晕了。
My God,you look absolutely stunning.
是吗？今天我特地去理发。
Well,I am having a good hair day.
- 见到你真好。 - 我也是。
- It's so good to see you. - Oh,you too.
我没事。
I'm okay.
对不起...罗斯.盖勒 班杰明赫伯
I'm sorry. Ross Geller,Benjamin Hobart.
很荣幸见到你。 我仰慕你都不知道多久了
It's an honor to meet you. I can't tell you how long..
我是说，你得的诺贝尔奖，喔！
I've been an admirer of your work. I mean,that Nobel Prize.
我得说 你是我从事科学工作的其中一个原因。
I mean,I have to tell you that you're one of the reasons I got into the field.
噢，是吗，我也是。
Well,likewise.
其实，不一样，我今早才第一次听到你的名字。
Not likewise. I'd never heard of you until this morning.
但，很高兴能见到你。
But it's nice to be nice.
- 我们...？ - 谢谢！
- Shall we? - Yeah. Thank you.
不能相信你选了这个餐馆！
I can't believe that you chose this restaurant.
-你还记得那天晚上吗？ -噢天啊，我都已经想不起了！
- Do you remember the night? - Oh,my God. I completely forgot.
天啊，我们居然又在这里碰头了！
Oh,my God,I can't believe they let us back in this place.
你当时不在场！
You weren't there.
是不在，但想想都好笑
No,but,you know,it's just a funny image.
想想你们两个 在这个餐馆，还...
You know,the two of you in this restaurant with the..
罗斯 我去洗手间的时候你能告诉班杰你的方案吗？
Ross,why don't you tell Benji about your proposal while I go to the ladies' room.
来吧，告诉我吧。
So tell me about it.
我们会在沙漠里进行挖掘.
Okay. Well,I would like to do a dig in the Painted Desert.
因为里面还有些地区还没完全开挖的。
There are still several areas that haven't been fully excavated.
-和查莉分手吧！ -什么？
- Break up with Charlie. - What?
什么？
What?
你刚才说 “和查莉分手”吗？
Did you just say,"Break up with Charlie"?
可以说是，也可以说不是 是，我是这样说了；不是，是我没有否认。
Well,yes and no. Yes,I did say it. And no,I didn't not say it.
-你不应该这样说的，是吗？ -对不起。
- Kind of inappropriate,don't you think? - Listen,I'm sorry.
因为我太久没有见她了！ 以前的感觉又涌上心头！
I just haven't seen her for so long,all these feelings are rushing back.
我又觉得喜欢上她了
I'm starting to realize how much I've missed her.
所以我想你和他分手
And I'm gonna need you to break up with her.
-你是说真的吗？ -如果你说是，那我就是认真的
- Are you serious? - If you say,yes,then I'm serious.
如果你说不是，那我就是开玩笑！
If you say,no,then I'm joking.
-不是！ -我开玩笑的！
- No. - Joking it is.
-嗨！对不起，我迟到了。 -嘿，和麦克谈得怎样？
- Hi,sorry I'm late. - Hey,how'd it go with Mike?
-他肯让你保留那幅画吗？ -不行，他实在很讨厌它
- Is he gonna let you keep the painting? - No,he really hates it.
但他肯让我留下我那盒头发！
But he's gonna let me keep my box of human hair.
所以我只能妥协了。 但好消息是，格拉达斯已经属于你了！
So you gotta pick your battles. But the good news is,Gladys is yours.
哇，那坏消息呢！？
Wow,what's the bad news?
-谁是格拉达斯？ -噢！她是我的手工作品，你见过啦
- Who's Gladys? - Oh,she's that work of art I made.
就是有个女人从画里面走出来的那幅画啊
You know,with the woman coming out of the frame.
噢，莫尼卡把她收下了吗？
And Monica gets to keep her?
放在这个房间里？我要嫉妒了！
In her house? I am so jealous.
噢！我不知道你也想要她啊！
I didn't know you wanted her too.
我..当然想要啊。
Well,I mean,sure,of course.
但..你已经给了莫尼卡了，所以...
But you already gave that to Monica,so..
-为了你，我可以放弃她。 -不行，我不可以让你这样做的。
- You know,I would give her up for you. - No,I couldn't let you do that.
-但我想这样做。 -但我不想你这样做。
- No,but I want to. - But I don't want you to.
-但我坚持！ -但我更坚持！
- But I insist. - But I insist harder.
女生们！停一停好吗？我们投硬币决定吧。
Girls. Girls. Stop. Okay,we'll flip a coin.
正面，她是瑞秋的 反面，她就是莫尼卡的。
Heads,she's Rachel's. Tails,she's Monica's.
-反面！莫尼卡，她是你的了！ -不行，它掉到你的食物里了
- Tails. Monica,she's yours. - No,that landed in your food.
不，没关系，该赢的就该赢。我太难过了。
No,no,that's okay. You won fair and square. I'm so sad.
然后红色的小松鼠把他所有的橡树果
Then the little red squirrel took all of his acorns..
放进他的小背包里,离开了
and put them in his little satchel and set off for..
好啦!有人开始烦啦 我看该睡觉了
Okay. Someone's getting a little fussy. I think it's time for bed.
小松鼠去哪了?
Where's the little red squirrel going?
嘿 乔！
Hey,Joe?
哦，太好了
Oh,that's so sweet.
-什么事？ -坏消息
- What's up? - Bad news.
我看过了带子并把它交给我的老板们 但他们不感兴趣。
I watched the tape and passed it along to my bosses and they weren't interested.
对不起，老兄。
I'm sorry,man.
-但...你看过这带子吗？ -是啊，我...我很喜欢啊！
- But you watched the tape? - Yeah,I liked it.
但...我的老板不喜欢。真他妈的可恶！
But my bosses didn't go for it. Stupid sons of bitches.
-你没有看过这带子。 -什么！？我当然看啦！
- You didn't watch the tape. - What? Of course I did.
你不推荐我是一回事，但你对我说谎？
Look,it's one thing not to cast me,but to lie to me?
-我没有说谎啊，我看了啦！ -你看，又说谎！
- I'm not lying to you. I watched it. - You lied again.
-我看了！ -继续说谎吧，匹诺曹！
- I watched it. - Keep going,Pinocchio.
-我看了！ -没有！ 你没看！
- I did. - No,you didn't.
我告诉你，我看了这带子。
I'm telling you,I watched the tape.
-你看过这带子吗？ -没有
- Did you watch the tape? - No.
嗨,听着,我知道我们中 只有一个人能得到认可
Hi. Look,I realize only one of us can get this grant.
而我也想祝福你们所有人好运
And I just wanted to wish both of you the best of luck.
你绕手指了（表示“不是真心的”）?
Are you crossing your fingers?
什么?这个?不,这个... 只是童年受伤的结果
What,this? No. This.. That's just the result of a childhood injury.
痊愈了！
I'm cured!
大家早上好
Good morning,everybody.
如果你们坐到座位上 我们就可以开始了
If you go ahead and take your seats we can get started.
实际上，赫伯博士 我能和你说句话吗?
Actually,Dr. Hobart,can I have a word with you?
你是...?
And you are?
- 罗斯 - 我知道,开玩笑的
- Ross. - I know. I'm kidding.
我只想说,昨晚...
Listen,I just want to say,last night..
晚餐不太好
Dinner was a little awkward.
-我只想知道我们之间没什么问题 -没问题!绝对没有!
- I just wanna make sure we're okay. - Oh,yeah. Absolutely.
- 你没有告诉查莉我说过什么吧? - 喔,没有,当然没有
- You didn't tell Charlie what I said,did you? - Oh,no. Of course not.
谢谢你,我想让你知道我尊重你 没有放弃她的决定
Well,thank you. I want you to know,I respect your decision not to give her up.
放弃她,是我一生中最大的错误
It was the biggest mistake I ever made in my whole life.
呃,除了这件事 还有我很蠢的把她的名字刺在肩膀上...
Well,that and tattooing her name on my shoulder..
就在昨天晚上..
last night stupidly.
真的?
Seriously?
我的诺贝尔奖可不是为了忘记
My Nobel Prize was not for moving on.
- 还难过吗？ - 一点也没有,祝今天好运!
- So no hard feelings? - None at all. Good luck today.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - Okay.
评选委员会选出你们三人于今天作最后评核。
All right. The selection committee has chosen the three of you as our finalists.
最终决定会基于你们如何回答我的问题。
The ultimate decision will be based on the answers you give to the questions I ask.
先从李博士开始吧。
We're gonna go ahead and start with Dr. Li.
李博士 你提出学界太依赖林奈分类系统。
You claim the field is too reliant on the Linnaean taxonomic system.
那你打算怎么解决这个问题？
How do you propose to correct this problem?
我相信解决办法在化石证据上
Well,I believe that the answers lie in the osteological evidence.
-我打算从那里入手 -很有趣
- I plan to begin there. - Interesting.
是吗？
I guess.
白莉博士，你的方案有一些挖掘工作 你会从哪里入手呢？
Dr. Biely,your proposal includes some fieldwork. Where might that take place?
首先是南达科他州的皮尔板岩地区。
Primarily in the Pierre Shale region of South Dakota.
当然，很好。那盖勒博士 你知道我的生日是什么时候吗？
Certainly. Very well. And Dr. Geller,when is my birthday?
什么？我...我...
What? I..
不能猜一下吗？
Care to venture a guess?
-5月12号？ -还差很远呢！
- May 12? - That's not even kind of close.
李博士，你需要多少个学生呢？
Dr. Li,how many graduate students will you need?
- 6个 -明白了，那白莉博士呢？
- Half a dozen. - I see. And Dr. Biely?
三个负责开掘，两个负责分析。
Three for excavation,and two for analysis.
当然。盖勒博士，1965年沙伦斯乐队哪首歌
Certainly. Dr. Geller,which 1965 Shirelles hit..
被英国入侵乐队盖过风头？
was later covered by a popular British Invasion band?
什么...？我需要6个学生。
What? I need six graduate students.
不是！对不起 答案是 “宝贝，就是你”
No,I'm sorry. We were looking for "Baby It's You."
宝贝，就是你。
"Baby It's You."
什么...？等等，等一下。
What? Wait just a minute.
我的问题没有一条是关于古生物学的。
None of my questions have anything to do with paleontology.
没错，我该道歉。 那最后一条问题
You're right,I apologize. Scratch the last question.
拼写单词Mboscodictiasaur。
Spell "Boscodictiasaur."
恩....我没有听过Mboscodictiasaur啊。
I've never heard of a "Boscodictiasaur."
是，我乱编的单词。快拼。
Yeah,I just made it up. Spell it.
-好的。B - O - S ... -不，开头有个不发音的“M”。
- Okay. B-O.. - No,it starts with a silent M.
噢，拜托！
Oh,come on!
我不明白乔伊，我讨厌被人称为骗子。
I can't believe Joey. I hate being called a liar.
但你是个骗子。
But you are a liar.
我刚刚怎么说的？
What did I just say?
-你还在啊？ -是的，
- Are you still here? - Yes.
我不仅是受伤害还被侮辱了 当我说我已经做了某事...
And I'm not just hurt,I'm insulted. When I tell somebody I did something..
好了好了... 我打断你一下好吗？ 首先，你说谎，对吗？
Okay,hold on,let me just stop you right there,okay? First,you lied. Right?
然后，你又说谎去圆谎，好吗？
Then you lied about lying,okay?
然后，你又再说谎去圆你刚才圆的谎 是不是？
Then you lied about lying about lying,okay?
所以在你说谎去圆你刚才 为圆谎...而说的谎...的那个谎言...
So before you lie about lying about lying about lying about lying..
不要说谎啦！
Stop lying.
为什么你这么肯定我没有看过那带子？
Why are you so sure I didn't watch this tape?
你想知道...? 你想知道为什么？
You wanna know why? You wanna know why?
事情发展得不错呢。
Well,this is going well.
这就是我知道你没看的原因了。
Here's how I know you didn't watch.
如果你看了这带子，你绝对不会没有话说的。
If you had seen what was on this tape,believe me,you'd have some comments.
听好，我收了很多钱才去拍这个广告
All right,remember,I got paid a lot of money for this..
而且只在日本地区放映。
and it only aired in Japan.
一级棒
Ichiban.
一级棒，男用唇膏！
Ichiban,lipstick for men.
这就是我知道你没看的原因！
And that's how I know you didn't watch the tape.
他真的是一条变色龙呢。
He really is a chameleon.
格拉达斯，给你的新家打个招呼吧！
Well,Gladys,say hello to your new home.
-我的...！ -哇！
- Oh,my. - Wow.
噢！她真漂亮，又显眼！
Oh,she is so nice and big.
噢！莫尼卡，你会把她放到什么地方 让格拉达斯显的得体呢？
Oh,Monica,where are you going to display Gladys,oh,so proudly?
-我还没决定放在哪里！ -那，不如放在电视机上面吧！
- I haven't really settled on a spot yet. - How about right above the TV?
这样的话，人们一进门就马上看得到了！
That way,it will be the first thing that you see when you walk in the door.
好啊，好啊！那你就可以丢掉那法国的海报了。
Yeah,yeah,and you can get rid of that French poster.
-我喜欢那海报啊！ -是吗？
- I like that poster. - Really?
它没有东西可以“冒”出来啊。
It doesn't have anything coming out of it.
又或者你的卧室里有空位吗？
Or maybe there's someplace for her in your bedroom?
-噢！你床头还空着呢！ -你还在这里住吗？
- There's nothing above your bed. - Are you still here?
愚蠢的诺贝尔奖获得者！
Stupid Nobel Prize winner.
对不起
I'm sorry
噢！嗨！你好！
Oh,hi. Hello.
呃，你是来问我古生物学的问题的吗？
Have you come to ask me some more paleontology-related questions?
呃...可能你要问我你祖母的小名吧？ 还是你马格莉特阿姨内裤的尺寸？
Your grandmother's nickname,perhaps? Ann-Margret's pant size?
我是来道歉的。 我想我对查莉的感情…
I've come here to apologize. I think I may have let my feelings..
影响到面试的程序了
for Charlie interfere with the interview process.
没有！哪里有！
No. Stop.
不管怎么说，我决定批准你的补助金。
Anyway,I decided to offer you the grant.
-真的吗？ -是的...只是还有一个...小条件...
- Really? - There is just one small stipulation.
-我要和查莉分手？ -嘿！你终于答对一次了！
- I have to break up with Charlie? - Hey,you got one right.
-你发神经。 -神经，还是...浪漫？
- You're crazy. - Crazy or romantic?
神经！
Crazy.
-还是... -出去！
- Or? - Get out!
噢！天啊！
Oh,my God.
-什么？ -乔伊，这..这...东西在这里干嘛？
- What? - Joey,what is this thing doing here?
我在莫尼卡那里拿过来的 她出了个很合理的价格。
I got her from Monica. She sold it to me for a very reasonable price.
-乔伊，我们不能留着这个！ -但它是原版的布菲作品啊...
- Joey,we're not keeping this. - But it's an original Buffay.
好的，没关系，你就留着吧。
All right,fine. You can keep it.
只要你不介意她四处游荡。
As long as you don't mind that she's haunted.
嘿？什么？什么？嘿！噢！什么！？
Hey,what? What?
有这样一个传说...她在半夜里会活过来。
Well,legend has it,Joey,that she comes alive when you're asleep.
她爬出这画框
She climbs out of the frame..
然后她拖着她这半个身体，爬在地板上
and then drags her half-a-body across the floor..
想办法去偷一双腿
just looking for legs to steal.
然后她用她唯一的一只手
And then with her one good hand..
慢慢、慢慢地
she slowly reaches up..
扭开门把手
and turns your doorknob.
拿走这没脚的妖怪！！
Get that legless witch out of here!
-嘿！我把它卖给乔伊了！ -所以我骗他这是鬼怪了
- Hey,I sold that to Joey. - Yeah,well,I told him it's haunted.
-我们都会玩这种把戏 -不行，太迟了，你不能退货！
- Two can play at this game. - Too late. You can't give it back.
-我当然可以！ -不，你不可以，她是你的 ！
- Oh,yes,I can. - No,you can't,she's yours.
-她是你的！ -是你的！
- She's yours. - She's yours.
-她是你的！ -嘿！
- She's yours. - Hey.
-她是我的！ -是我的！
- She's mine. - She's mine.
-她是我的！ -她是我的！
你们啊！不用为她争吵了。
You guys,you don't have to fight over her anymore.
谁得不到格拉达斯，就把格林妮斯拿回去吧。
Whoever doesn't get Gladys,gets Glynnis.
-我要格拉达斯。 -她是我的！
- I want Gladys. - She's mine.
-她是我的！ -她是我的！
- She's mine. - She's mine.
你好，乔伊先生（日语）
Konichiwa，Joey sang
不要不要.你不要这样了
No,no. You don't get to do that.
很抱歉我没有把你的带子给他们。
I know. Look,I'm sorry I didn't give them your tape.
我保证，下次无论合不合适我都会把你推荐上去的。
And I promise next time to submit you,whether I think you're right or not.
重点不是这个啊钱德。 重点是，你说了谎
That's not the point,Chandler. The point is that you lied.
我知道，你说的对 我要做什么你才能原谅我？
I know. You're right. What's it gonna take for you to forgive me?
噢 天啊！
Oh,my God.
太完美了！
Excellent.
现在你该说什么？
Now what do you say?
说谎是不对的！
Lying is wrong.
还有呢？...还有呢？
And? And?
我是个漂亮小女生
I'm a pretty little girl.
我早就知道啦！
I knew it.
你的前男友是个疯子。
Your ex-boyfriend is insane.
-他是个有个性的人 -不是,才不是呢
- He is a character. - No,no,no.
查尔斯・纳尔逊・赖利（演员）才是
Charles Nelson Reilly is a character.
- 谁? - 查尔斯・纳尔逊・赖利
- Who? - Charles Nelson Reilly.
《幽灵与未亡人》和《比赛》的主演？
The Ghost and Mrs. Muir? Match Game?
你小时侯都没得过病吗?
Were you never sick as a child?
- 随便啦！ 你得到那笔补助了吗？ - 没有，你想知道为什么吗？
- Whatever. Did you get the grant? - No. And you wanna know why?
因为你的前男友还是爱着你。
Because your ex-boyfriend is still in love with you.
-什么？ -没错
- What? - Yeah.
他没有给我那笔补助，就因为我没有放弃你。
He refused me because I wouldn't give you up.
班杰不会还爱着我的。 因为当时是他抛弃我
Benji isn't in love with me. I mean,he broke up with me.
-而且，他是个有道德的人。 -是吗？？？
- And besides,he's a very ethical man. - Really?
在补助调查中问这种问题：
Is it ethical to ask someone in a grant review:
“谁是《超狗》的配音员？”  很认真吗？
"Who was the voice of Underdog?"
我肯定他是在开玩笑，罗斯。
I'm sure he was just joking.
如果你不相信我，我们去找他对质吧。
If you don't believe me,let's go talk to him.
可以告诉你 他没有问过我一个关于考古学的问题
I'm telling you,he didn't ask me one paleontological question.
-真的吗？ -哦，不是，他问了我一个。
- Seriously? - Oh,I'm sorry. No,he did ask me one:
呃...怎么拼Mboscodictiosaur
"How do you spell Boscodictiasaur?"
和刚果的Mbosco湖拼法一样，那是M-B-O...
Well,if it's like the Lake Mbosco in Congo,then M-B-O..
可恶！
Damn it.
盖勒博士...？查莉  你...你到这来干什么？
Dr. Geller. Charlie,what are you doing here?
我要你告诉他一切。
I want you to tell her everything.
告诉他你想和我做的交易，那些神经病的问题
About the deal you tried to make with me,about the crazy questions you..
沃利・考克斯！他就是《超狗》的配音！
Wally Cox. That's the voice of Underdog.
就如之前的面谈我告诉你的一样
Like I tried to tell you in the interview..
这个补助基金不是为了这些无聊的知识而设的
this grant is not based on your knowledge of pretty useless trivia.
不！不！不！别这样！ 我要你看着她的眼睛，告诉她真相。
No,don't do that. I want you to look her in the eyes and tell her the truth.
班杰？
Benji?
是的，的确是这样。我之前简直是乱来。 但这都是因为我还爱着你。
All right. It's true. I behaved horribly,but it's only because I still love you.
只要你回到我身边，我可以做任何事。
And I would do anything to have you back in my life.
太少了，太迟了，班杰！
Too little,too late,Benji.
-我不敢相信。 -我真不应该离开你
- I can't believe this. - I never should've broken up with you.
我无时无刻不想起你。 难道你一点都没有想起我?
I think about you all the time. Do you ever still think about me?
没有!
No.
-有! -什么?
- Yes. - What?
我不知道该说什么好了，班杰。 这一切实在太...
I don't know what to say,Benji. This is all so..
浪漫了
romantic.
或者...
Or?
我知道，或者我做得太过火了
I know I may be way out of bounds here..
但我们还有机会在一起吗？
but is there any chance you would take me back?
或者可以...
Maybe.
甜心，你们的对话让我觉得有点不舒服了。
Sweetie,this conversation is starting to make me a little uncomfortable.
噢 天啊！我很抱歉，但...
Oh,God. I am so sorry,but..
我是说...我们之前有太多的过去了...
I mean,there's so much history between us,you know?
我也觉得抱歉...
I'm sorry too.
-我爱你! -噢! 我也爱你!
- I love you. - I love you too.
好了,够了。我们算是完了！
Okay,that's it,we are seeing other people.
格拉达斯?
Gladys?
哈哈哈，这个星期的第三次了。 老兄，你怎么还没长大啊？
For the third time this week. Man,this does not get old.
-你真可恶！ -不要这么孩子气啦！
- You're mean! - Oh,don't be such a baby. Please.